Robles Aquije Roger David

+51 979338549

dra3897@gmail.com

Profile

Nice to meet you, I am a graduate Software Engineer with experience in web development, I also have experience as a technical consultant in SAP Cloud Application Studio for more than 1 year. I am a person committed to continuous learning, in addition to always being willing to acquire and improve skills and knowledge in related tools and technologies to progress in my career.

Skills

- javascript
- React
- HTML and CSS
- SCRUM
- Spanish Language

- MySQL, MongoDB, Firebase
- Bootstrap, jQuery.
- NodeJS (Express)

Professional experience

Technical Consultant

seidor peru

dec. 2021- Apr. 2023

- In charge of developing solutions to technical problems using SAP Cloud Application Studio, contributing to the improvement of client systems.
- Provide support to colleagues from other areas on technical issues, as well as functional issues based on SAP technology.
- Performed the taking of requirements, as well as clearing the doubts of the clients in the meetings

Software programmer

sept. 2021 - Jan. 2022

Ulead International

- I contributed to an adequate and effective interconnection between the training offer and the demand in the labor market.
- Resolution of practical cases, creation and improvement of web pages, developing strategies based on their acquired knowledge.
- I acquired greater fluency in social and personal skills related to the work environment to achieve the objectives.

Front End Developer

aug. 2018 - Jun. 2021

General Services Nelica SAC

- Streamlined web page development using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript along with tools like Bootstrap and jQuery, enabling faster project delivery.
- Develop mobile apps in Android Studio using XML for UI design and Java for programming, reducing the workload on UI developers.
- Assisted in the productivity and growth of less experienced co-workers through good guidance and good behavior.

Education

Bachelor of Software Engineering

Technological University of Peru

Additional Information

- Belonging to the Fifth and Upper Tenthg
- Knowledge in design with AdobeXD and Figma
- 1st place in hackathon "hackatu 2022" organized by ATU 2021 (Peru)
- 1st place in hackathon "solutions of the future" UTP 2019
- 2nd place in "UTP El comercio" hackathon
- Love for physical activity
- Knowledge of Backend languages such as JAVA and PHP
- Knowledge of Excel, Drawio and Bizagi
- Management of development environments: Netbeans, Visual Studio, Balsamiq and Visual Studio Code
- Course "React: From zero to expert (hooks and MERN)"
- Course "React Native: Native applications for IOS and Android"
- SCRUM methodology fundamentals course

Some of my Projects

Tasks APP (ToDo React App)

Vite + React (endearing-sawine-02220c.netlify.app)

Gift Expert APP (React + Gift API)

Gifts Project (remarkable-gnome-5c986e.netlify.app)

Journal APP (React + Firebase + Cloudinary)

https://rainbow-nougat-1f561f.netlify.app/

Calendario APP (MongoDB, Express, React, NodeJS)

https://node-mongodb-api-zvgs.onrender.com/

aug. 2022

Social Networks and Certificates

- GitHub: https://github.com/DavidRoblesAquije
- LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/davidroblesaquije/
- Master in JavaScript: JS, jQuery, Angular, NodeJS: <u>UC-183b7ce7-7c77-4566-8d02-41d0ce4516f7.jpg (1600×1190) (udemy-certificate.s3.amazonaws.com)</u>
- React: Hooks and MERN
 <u>UC-4b3ad07b-fce0-46a1-89ce-9fbfdf26c4c6.jpg (1600×1190) (udemy-certificate.s3.amazonaws.com)</u>
- SCRUM Fundamentals Certified
 https://drive.google.com/file/d/1YbWYZWOmIF0Q9BAMVVQDK7Ip6PJ-7mAI/view?usp=sharing